So answer me truthfully.
What did you do to her?
Huh?
I know you came to the apartment
by yourself yesterday.
Yesterday?
I declined.
I formally told her that
I couldn't go out with her.
Because I was going to choose Adagaki Aki.
#9 "It's Been Called Love and Affection"
Anyway, if she's missing, let's look for her.
Can't you use GPS?
She left without her cell phone
and wallet, so we can't track her.
Did they just ignore me?!
I see. Then she probably
couldn't have gotten far.
We might be able to find her if we split up.
You'll all help, won't you?
Of course!
Shidou-san, will you take
us closer to the apartment?
Yes. Please get in.
Those who can't fit in
the car, go with Makabe.
Since he seems to know where it is.
I guess I'll go in the car...
M-Me, too.
I...
I didn't know you went to her apartment.
Y-You said to speed things up, right?
That's not what I meant when I said that.
Yoshino, hurry up.
No comment to the very end?
Do I really matter so little?
Damn it! Don't think about that now.
Jeez...
Where did that commando princess go?
But exactly how are we
supposed to find her?
We don't have any clues.
But in addition to her weak constitution,
she doesn't have her wallet, right?
Which means...
It'll be within walking
distance of the apartment,
and somewhere she can stay cool
for free. That's important.
Yeah... I looked around everywhere
that seemed like it'd be cool,
but she wasn't there.
I see. Got it.
Huh?
No, let's not look in the pond just yet.
Yeah, I'd like to presume
that she's still alive.
Then the only place left is...
If she's not here, I'm out of ideas.
Makabe?
A mirage?
Oh, wait. She's real.
What in the world are you babbling about?
A condescending tone and a flat chest.
Definitely Adagaki Aki.
You thought she might be at school, too?
What?
N-Nothing.
She may be aggravating, but it
seems we had the same idea.
She usually traveled by car,
so I thought this was about the only place
she could go without really knowing the area.
Well, it was a miss.
I went everywhere that had a roof, but...
Where should we look next?
Adagaki-san, I thought you
didn't like Fujinomiya-san.
Huh?
Er, sorry. I was just kinda surprised...
I guess I didn't think you'd go this far.
I don't like her, even now.
That perverted catgirl...
It's just... I feel bad for her
since you rejected her.
Having someone you like look the other way
is a very sad thing.
How am I...
supposed to take what she just said?
If that's what you think,
why do you do that yourself?
You give any guy who tries to get close to
you awful nicknames and push them away.
Do you think guys don't
have feelings or something?
Even for me...
Suddenly having my feelings
thrown back in my face,
and then getting them stomped on...
So I just didn't want her to wallow
in self-torment about it anymore...
Makabe?
Adagaki-san...
Do you happen to remember
the nickname "Pig's Foot"?
I want so badly to tell you right now...
that I was the "Pig's Foot"
you rejected that one time.
Pig's Foot?
Ow!
A paper airplane? Where did it...
The roof...
After I spotted it in your room,
I became curious and had
Shidou purchase them.
I've read volume three so many times!
Hey!
She said that she was reading
"Rose-eyed Steroid."
It's right around when the heroine gets
rejected by her beloved senpai...
That scene on the roof was just...
What I have in my hands
are love letters that have
lost their destination.
Give it up, Momo...
Senpai has someone else he likes.
Goodbye,
Senpai.
What the hell are you doing up here?
Huh?
That voice... It couldn't be...
What the hell are you doing up here?
I had a feeling that you would come.
You mentioned that you
liked the rooftop scene
in "Rose-eyed Steroid" volume 3.
But don't do this.
You don't have the strength to do
the same thing Momo did, do you?
Yes. I think I realize that now.
Hey—
Are you all right? Hey! Hey!
Makabe! What happened?
Adagaki-san! Contact Shidou-san!
A-All right.
Why do this to yourself?
I love you.
I wonder if she's okay.
Shidou-san.
How's Fujinomiya-san?
She seems to be stable.
Thank goodness.
Adagaki Aki-san.
Neko-sama would like to speak to you.
To me?
She is extremely exhausted.
If you can, please keep it short.
R-Right...
This feels like a final farewell.
Don't say that, Koiwai-san!
Now, now. She just said she was fine.
I wasn't wrong, was I?
It's true that my heart wavered.
But it didn't feel right, so I pushed her away.
For my plan... For my revenge.
Even if I had given her a more
favorable answer in this situation,
nothing would've come of it.
I shouldn't be wrong.
Damn it.
I...
Makabe.
Apparently, you're next.
Me?
What did they talk about?
There's no way I can ask
her about that now.
Fujinomiya Neko
Come in.
Fujinomiya-san...
Let's talk about the past,
Masamune-sama.
Being alive is a wonderful thing.
That's why I didn't really
feel any discontent.
Seichou Girls' Private Academy
Fujinomiya-sama!
Neko-sama!
Onee-sama!
That was a lovely student
council speech you gave.
I was so moved.
Thank you very much.
U-Um, Onee-sama... If it's all right,
would you like to come to my
family's villa this weekend?
Yours?
It's my birthday.
If you were to celebrate
it with me, I would...
My kouhai are all so sweet.
They're such good girls.
If you would have me, I would be happy to.
Thank you so much!
There's a riding ground for
horses and a tennis court,
so would you like to join
me before the party?
Huh?
What are you thinking, asking
Neko-sama to play tennis?
She's so frail!
I'm so sorry! I didn't know.
It's common knowledge.
I can't believe you'd try to get closer to
Neko-sama when you don't know that.
What should I do?
What should you do?
Figure it out.
It's fine, everyone.
Oh...
What a silly story.
Surgery? Overseas?
Fujinomiya
If nothing is done, your
condition will only worsen.
Will you consider trying it?
How promising is this prospect?
No, sorry.
Please forget that I ever mentioned it.
It's fine, Grandfather.
I don't mind trying it.
I see.
But I just have one request...
What is it?
I...
would like to fall in love.
When this all became a
life-or-death situation,
rather than the usual worries or
fears most people would have,
I realized that there was no hope.
I wanted to experience love, at least.
But why me?
Who knows?
I just randomly picked your photo
out of the mountain of photos
I had for potential suitors.
Randomly?!
Yes.
Was it a lottery?!
You could call it that.
Also, I never heard anything
about being a potential suitor!
It's not uncommon among prestigious families
for this to happen to the children,
unbeknownst to them, is it?
Look, look! Hasn't my
Maa-kun become so handsome?
Was it that old hag?!
If that's why, there's no way we could've
found out anything by researching.
Yoshino-san is very efficient,
but she couldn't trace the
thoughts of a sickly person.
So you knew.
So, how did it feel to try it?
Well...
The trial and error was fun,
and I thought you and I were exactly alike.
You and I?
Yes. You talk about love and affection
for the purpose of your goal,
but the truth is hidden in fog.
Shallow and empty...
In the end, the lie was discovered,
and my feelings didn't reach.
But I don't have any regrets.
Huh?
I went into everything superficially,
but the fluttery feeling of one-sided love...
The pain of being rejected...
I was able to experience them firsthand.
Masamune-sama, what about you?
Will you keep walking
down the same path as me?
I...
Will you reach the same point I have?
No!
Really?
I hope that is the case.
I must say it's rather
exhausting to talk this long.
Are you okay?
When I regain my strength,
I believe I will be going far away.
So, Masamune-sama...
Thank you very much for the lovely memories.
I wonder what Masamune-kun and
Fujinomiya-san are talking about.
To tell you the truth, I actually
liked Masamune-kun, too.
Are you surprised?
A little.
Did you really think it wasn't obvious?
That's what surprised me.
I sometimes think I might
regret not telling him,
but I think it was better
to keep my feelings inside.
I'm able to hang out with you all now.
I hope that wasn't the
case for Fujinomiya-san.
Yeah, sure.
I-Is it okay that I'm here?
Masamune-kun likes Adagaki-san, right?
I wonder how Adagaki-san feels.
Looks like her stomach's reached its limit.
Huh?
She's sad that she has to hold back.
Oh, right. Yeah, I totally get that.
Love can be so sad.
That's not what I meant.
But...
That might also be the case to some degree.
Masamune-kun!
Um... Makabe...
Milady.
Shidou.
It appears that your classmates
have left the hospital.
I see. Thank you for informing me.
I realize I may be out of line,
but are you sure you want to let him go?
This is fine.
What Masamune-sama said is the truth.
And...
It's true that he made me remember.
Wedding Party
Neko.
Maa-kun, we're going to take a picture!
My, they're so adorable.
These two sort of look alike, don't they?
All right, here we go.
I thought you and I were exactly alike.
You talk about love and affection
for the purpose of your goal,
but the truth is hidden in fog.
Shallow and empty...
In the end, the lie was discovered,
and my feelings didn't reach.
Lies will be discovered...
That's right...
I thought something was strange,
so I couldn't trust you.
So that's...
what I'll look like in the future?
Will you keep walking
down the same path as me?
Damn it. Damn it!
What am I so worried about?
Don't think about unnecessary things!
I'm not going to waver now!
I'm going to make Adagaki Aki look my way,
and then...
I'll throw her away in the best way possible.
Are you heading out, milady?
I'm just going out to the garden.
I'm not going outside.
Okay. Have fun.
That should be enough.
Please stop trying to act so tough.
Tough?
As you can see, I was completely
and utterly rejected.
Masamune-sama is a sincere person.
What reason could you have
to deny his love for you?
Love? It's not like love.
I mean, it's true.
The Commando Catgirl thing was a mistake,
and there's no reason to get mad.
So... should I like him?
No.
No, no, no, no! That's not possible!
I mean, it's Makabe! That
thoughtless, stupid man!
He says whatever sounds good
whenever he opens his mouth.
You're so pathetic, Masamune.
You need to straighten up more!
I can't, Aki-chan!
That's right.
If you want to call something
"love," that was love.
Those chubby little cheeks,
his tummy that had rolls worth tugging on...
He was so cute.
Who's there?!
Maa-kun! Maa-kun's...
What? Did something happen?
Maa-kun's saying he's going to run away.
Just like that one song!
You're overreacting again.
I'm sure he's just off to train
by going jogging again.
That's right.
I'm going to retrain myself since
I became naïve at some point.
I'm going to carry out my original plan.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Sniffle.
I'm going to get rid of any unneeded fat
and build up some new muscles
and ways of being hot.
I'm sorry I scared you.
Who are you?
I wonder who I could be.
Why don't you guess?
Could you actually be...
Masamune?
Hey, it's been a while, Aki-chan.
I'm back.